let savollar14 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "coach",
        answer: "A. murabbiy",
        options: [
            "A. murabbiy",
            "B. o'yinchi",
            "C. hakam",
            "D. tomoshabin"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "to control",
        answer: "B. nazorat qilmoq",
        options: [
            "A. e'tiborsiz qoldirmoq",
            "B. nazorat qilmoq",
            "C. yo'qotmoq",
            "D. to'xtatmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "description",
        answer: "D. tavsif",
        options: [
            "A. tushuntirish",
            "B. ta'rif",
            "C. tarjima",
            "D. tavsif"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "direct",
        answer: "C. to'g'ridan-to'g'ri",
        options: [
            "A. bilvosita",
            "B. murakkab",
            "C. to'g'ridan-to'g'ri",
            "D. chetlab o'tmoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "exam",
        answer: "A. imtihon",
        options: [
            "A. imtihon",
            "B. dars",
            "C. mashq",
            "D. uy vazifasi"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "example",
        answer: "B. misol",
        options: [
            "A. mavzu",
            "B. misol",
            "C. tushuntirish",
            "D. model"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "limit",
        answer: "C. chegara",
        options: [
            "A. erkinlik",
            "B. imkoniyat",
            "C. chegara",
            "D. istisno"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "local",
        answer: "A. mahalliy",
        options: [
            "A. mahalliy",
            "B. xalqaro",
            "C. milliy",
            "D. uzoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "magical",
        answer: "D. sehrli",
        options: [
            "A. oddiy",
            "B. zerikarli",
            "C. normal",
            "D. sehrli"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "mail",
        answer: "B. maktub",
        options: [
            "A. elektron pochta",
            "B. maktub",
            "C. xabar",
            "D. paket"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "novel",
        answer: "C. roman",
        options: [
            "A. she'r",
            "B. jurnal",
            "C. roman",
            "D. hisobot"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "outline",
        answer: "A. reja",
        options: [
            "A. reja",
            "B. mazmun",
            "C. kirish",
            "D. xulosa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "poet",
        answer: "D. shoir",
        options: [
            "A. roman yozuvchisi",
            "B. jurnalist",
            "C. muharrir",
            "D. shoir"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "to print",
        answer: "C. bosib chiqarmoq",
        options: [
            "A. yozmoq",
            "B. o'qimoq",
            "C. bosib chiqarmoq",
            "D. yubormoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "scene",
        answer: "A. sahna",
        options: [
            "A. sahna",
            "B. film",
            "C. bob",
            "D. kitob"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "sheet",
        answer: "B. varoq",
        options: [
            "A. kitob",
            "B. varoq",
            "C. qog'oz",
            "D. sahifa"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "silly",
        answer: "D. ahmoqona",
        options: [
            "A. aqlli",
            "B. jiddiy",
            "C. dono",
            "D. ahmoqona"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "store",
        answer: "C. do'kon",
        options: [
            "A. maktab",
            "B. ofis",
            "C. do'kon",
            "D. zavod"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "to suffer",
        answer: "A. azoblanmoq",
        options: [
            "A. azoblanmoq",
            "B. kulmoq",
            "C. o'ynamoq",
            "D. kuylamoq"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "technology",
        answer: "B. texnologiya",
        options: [
            "A. tabiat",
            "B. texnologiya",
            "C. san'at",
            "D. musiqa"
        ]
    }
];
